{
    "id": "a2e995479503494d909a95629d1a60e5",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This material is different ………………… that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You should explain this ………………… them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been absent ………………… Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t been to the theatre ………………… a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He goes ……………….. school by car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a comfortable house to live ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They are called …………………. different names.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not spend money ………………. luxuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I gave him a chair to sit ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The new term begins …………………. June 1st.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He poured the tea ………………….. the mug.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he was very pleased …………………. my work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}